<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[KPGrid]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[KPGrid]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 11:02:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Restructuring & Insolvency  + Add to binder Practicing in one of the major restructuring and insolvency areanas of our times, we have a recognized leading edge restructuring practice built around complex creditor requirements  We are at the forefront of international restructuring, distressed investment and insolvency law and finance across sectors and industries. We work programmatically to incorporate the latest global ideas and developments in the laws and finance of insolvency, such as the use of arbitrage opportunities in the bond and secondary distressed debt, and the primary corporate finance markets, for consensual and non-consensual restructuring, into the substantive and procedural arsenal we bring to the service of investors, creditors and turnaround advisers.   Partners at KP have had leading roles in some of the most significant cross-border restructurings over the past decade, and participate actively in the principal global law and practice shaping forums.   We have a deep understanding of the dynamics of contentious and non-contentious restructurings, and have applied principles and structures for cramming down equity and sub-par dissenting debt, to empower corporate actions and priority pre and post-petition funding, while preserving operations, in many usual and unusual stressed and distressed scenarios.   We develop clear and actionable pathways for the use of restructuring and insolvency proceedings in the service of privatization projects, and strategies for the efficient investment in bad financial and non-financial asset portfolios.   We regularly train investment bankers, financiers and international restructuring advisers, into the intricacies of domestic law and process, and participate in professional working groups engaged in the formulation of streamlined distressed investment models.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.kp-lf.com/Expertise/LegalAreas/RestructuringInsolvency/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9aae7cf2-044d-40d0-ba46-69d1a7128f5a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 11:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NOMOS]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>NOMOS</h1><p>Γνωστοποίηση της Απορρόφησης της NOMOS και της INTRACOM IT SERVICES από την INTRASOFT INTERNATIONAL με έδρα το Λουξεμβούργο</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/cb0e633d40f24d8912abca7e296e8a3f23f0844b.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://lawdb.intrasoftnet.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f03acfd4-f4d8-4738-a784-6a4c7a4f0801</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 10:44:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Areios Pagos - Supreme Court of Greece]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Areios Pagos - Supreme Court of Greece</h1></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.areiospagos.gr/en/INDEX.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a2ddf1d1-5011-4ed8-9bad-6bf26d97e8d4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 10:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Γιατί η κυβέρνηση δεν "κοιτάζει" προς τις κάλπες, της Δώρας Αντωνίου | Kathimerini]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Γιατί η κυβέρνηση δεν "κοιτάζει" προς τις κάλπες, της Δώρας Αντωνίου | Kathimerini</h1><p>"Ο Μητσοτάκης ζητάει εκλογές εκ του ασφαλούς, γιατί ξέρει ότι τώρα δεν υπάρχει περίπτωση να γίνουν. Είναι καθαρά επικοινωνιακή κίνηση, το έχουμε κάνει και εμείς στο παρελθόν". Από το επιτελείο του πρωθυπουργού Αλέξη Τσίπρα δείχνουν απαξιωτική διάθεση έναντι του αιτήματος για πρόωρη προσφυγή στις κάλπες, που διατύπωσε ο επικεφαλής της αξιωματικής αντιπολίτευσης στη Βουλή την περασμένη Τρίτη.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6b2864666090928a411013a8785028102384a344.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.kathimerini.gr/855417/article/epikairothta/politikh/giati-h-kyvernhsh-den-koitazei-pros-tis-kalpes?platform=hootsuite</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e0c5bbac-86ec-4045-b0d9-cd415baf2a4f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:58:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | A Word from our Partners]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | A Word from our Partners</h1><p>At the heart of the firm's vision lies a simple idea: to discipline the provision of advice with the knowledge of what passes the stringent tests of litigation or arbitration; and to enrich the methodologies for the resolution of disputes with the analytical understanding of the economics and business intricacies of sectors and industries, and of each specific entity and set circumstances, where the firm is retained to act.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/889018c645a31e38869fb52889fddb5512d07c8a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-a-word-from-our-partners/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6a98f10b-945c-4472-8b52-4a4b3c674095</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:43:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome to KP]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome to KP</h1><p>Christina Papachristopoulou is a finance, corporate & commercial, and capital markets partner, specializing in the entire spectrum of finance transactions, structures and methodologies and complex corporate transactions.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2dfbbaacd166818dd4bac7a77b3702bcf7650d11.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/welcome-to-kp/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">03a435c9-ae1f-4a0f-ba1f-01a19c96ac8e</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:43:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Expertise]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Expertise</h1><p>KP is a broad niche practice serving international and domestic commercial and industrial corporates, financial institutions, and natural persons facing critical and high impact situations, in contentious and non-contentious matters within its fields of expertise.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/889018c645a31e38869fb52889fddb5512d07c8a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-expertise/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7ad23cb0-507d-43f1-8ae1-5305f5a231ad</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:40:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Capital Markets]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Capital Markets</h1><p>We bring broad and deep insights about local regulatory, cultural and transactional particularities to the service of sophisticated capital markets transactions. Capital markets partners have significant track records in capital market transactions, including IPO's, secondary offerings and market and OTC transactions in the Athens Exchange and foreign organized markets, such as the AIM market of the LSE.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-capital-markets/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d10839-5f76-4028-a7fc-88019ae18763</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Construction Disputes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Construction Disputes</h1><p>We have advised on the adoption and improvement of documentation systems and processes for unplanned events and contingencies, as well as on pre- and post-delivery expertise and arbitration, and have successfully arbitrated and litigated construction quality and warranty issues, engineer fees, specification and bill of quantities disputes, change orders, scope changes and interference claims, in managed, unit and fixed price projects.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-construction-disputes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">45a94fd8-beb0-44e8-9ed9-b4ef2e2c5a98</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Media Disputes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Media Disputes</h1><p>Drawing on our rich litigation capabilities, we bring our media disputes practice to the service of in-house and professional crisis-management experts leading reputation and goodwill protection projects, emphasising interim and conservatory measures prevention over restitution and damage claims, where objectively possible.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8c9dfbba815b3a3022853374496308be398a74fc.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-media-disputes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">786b87ce-e3cc-465c-807b-26c94f24180a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>