<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[KP Law Firm]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[KP Law Firm]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 12:40:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Arbitration]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Arbitration</h1><p>The drastic shift of traditional dispute resolution paradigms of the past decade, driven by technological progress, economic innovation and globalization, highlights the importance of cross-border effectiveness, technical proficiency, speed and finality of dispute resolution methods. Rhetoric and volume-billed mega-files are out; economic analysis, clear definintion of the subject matter of disputes, and incisive expertise are in.
 
Modern commercial arbitration responds effectively and efficiently to each of these requirements, and the disputes partners at KP have established track records arbitrating a wide array of business-critical disputes. We have acted for claimants and respondents in international and domestic arbitration, institutional and ad hoc, in a variety of sectors, including procurement, construction, distribution and supply chain, alongside general commercial disputes.
 
We have considerable experience with complex proceedings involving multiple parties and parallel multi-forum tactical litigation, spanning all procedural stages, from pre-trial and trial discovery, to interim and conservatory measures, to the stage of enforcement of arbitral awards in multiple jurisdictions.
 
We have pursued and defended applications to set aside arbitral awards in Greece, and have assisted as Greek counsel in proceedings to set aside arbitral awards in foreign jurisdictions. We maintain an active presense in prominent academic and professional fora dedicated to the law and practice of international commercial and investment arbitration, and invest programmatically in staying at the forefront of current developments in expertise, forensics, remote taking of evidence and e-discovery, so that we are at all times able to advise and drive a fast, efficient and effective process.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/dbf7bf5e-e5e4-4156-950e-9fff1e4732a8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/arbitration/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">748edb91-47aa-4c50-8733-862b7965c47c</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Restructuring & Insolvency </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.kp-lf.com/Expertise/LegalAreas/RestructuringInsolvency/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9aae7cf2-044d-40d0-ba46-69d1a7128f5a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 12:10:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | A Word from our Partners]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | A Word from our Partners</h1><p>At the heart of the firm's vision lies a simple idea: to discipline the provision of advice with the knowledge of what passes the stringent tests of litigation or arbitration; and to enrich the methodologies for the resolution of disputes with the analytical understanding of the economics and business intricacies of sectors and industries, and of each specific entity and set circumstances, where the firm is retained to act.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/889018c645a31e38869fb52889fddb5512d07c8a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-a-word-from-our-partners/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6a98f10b-945c-4472-8b52-4a4b3c674095</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:43:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome to KP]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome to KP</h1><p>Christina Papachristopoulou is a finance, corporate & commercial, and capital markets partner, specializing in the entire spectrum of finance transactions, structures and methodologies and complex corporate transactions.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2dfbbaacd166818dd4bac7a77b3702bcf7650d11.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/welcome-to-kp/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">03a435c9-ae1f-4a0f-ba1f-01a19c96ac8e</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:43:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Expertise]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Expertise</h1><p>KP is a broad niche practice serving international and domestic commercial and industrial corporates, financial institutions, and natural persons facing critical and high impact situations, in contentious and non-contentious matters within its fields of expertise.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/889018c645a31e38869fb52889fddb5512d07c8a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-expertise/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7ad23cb0-507d-43f1-8ae1-5305f5a231ad</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:40:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Capital Markets]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Capital Markets</h1><p>We bring broad and deep insights about local regulatory, cultural and transactional particularities to the service of sophisticated capital markets transactions. Capital markets partners have significant track records in capital market transactions, including IPO's, secondary offerings and market and OTC transactions in the Athens Exchange and foreign organized markets, such as the AIM market of the LSE.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-capital-markets/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d10839-5f76-4028-a7fc-88019ae18763</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Construction Disputes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Construction Disputes</h1><p>We have advised on the adoption and improvement of documentation systems and processes for unplanned events and contingencies, as well as on pre- and post-delivery expertise and arbitration, and have successfully arbitrated and litigated construction quality and warranty issues, engineer fees, specification and bill of quantities disputes, change orders, scope changes and interference claims, in managed, unit and fixed price projects.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-construction-disputes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">45a94fd8-beb0-44e8-9ed9-b4ef2e2c5a98</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Media Disputes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Media Disputes</h1><p>Drawing on our rich litigation capabilities, we bring our media disputes practice to the service of in-house and professional crisis-management experts leading reputation and goodwill protection projects, emphasising interim and conservatory measures prevention over restitution and damage claims, where objectively possible.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8c9dfbba815b3a3022853374496308be398a74fc.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-media-disputes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">786b87ce-e3cc-465c-807b-26c94f24180a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>