<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[KPGrid]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[KPGrid]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:35:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Capital Markets]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Capital Markets</h1><p>We bring broad and deep insights about local regulatory, cultural and transactional particularities to the service of sophisticated capital markets transactions. Capital markets partners have significant track records in capital market transactions, including IPO's, secondary offerings and market and OTC transactions in the Athens Exchange and foreign organized markets, such as the AIM market of the LSE.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-capital-markets/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d10839-5f76-4028-a7fc-88019ae18763</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:35:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Construction Disputes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Construction Disputes</h1><p>We have advised on the adoption and improvement of documentation systems and processes for unplanned events and contingencies, as well as on pre- and post-delivery expertise and arbitration, and have successfully arbitrated and litigated construction quality and warranty issues, engineer fees, specification and bill of quantities disputes, change orders, scope changes and interference claims, in managed, unit and fixed price projects.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-construction-disputes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">45a94fd8-beb0-44e8-9ed9-b4ef2e2c5a98</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Media Disputes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Media Disputes</h1><p>Drawing on our rich litigation capabilities, we bring our media disputes practice to the service of in-house and professional crisis-management experts leading reputation and goodwill protection projects, emphasising interim and conservatory measures prevention over restitution and damage claims, where objectively possible.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8c9dfbba815b3a3022853374496308be398a74fc.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-media-disputes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">786b87ce-e3cc-465c-807b-26c94f24180a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Procurement & Construction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Procurement & Construction</h1><p>e are well placed to respond to the demand for a state-of-the art legal service, drawing on a combination of strengths in procurement and construction, finance foreign direct investment and disputes, alongside general corporate and commercial law,</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-procurement-and-construction/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2268f9cd-a749-4d6d-af2d-8f8e8e276b4b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Restructuring & Insolvency]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Restructuring & Insolvency</h1><p>We are at the forefront of international restructuring, distressed investment and insolvency law and finance across sectors and industries. We work programmatically to incorporate the latest global ideas and developments in the laws and finance of insolvency, such as the use of arbitrage opportunities in the bond and secondary distressed debt, and the primary corporate finance markets, for consensual and non-consensual restructuring, into the substantive and procedural arsenal we bring to the service of investors, creditors and turnaround advisers.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-restructuring-and-insolvency/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c9519d38-bca1-4a7b-82fc-58a6a7a2ec53</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Service inquiries]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Service inquiries</h1><p>If you are already in touch with one of our partners, you are welcome to address all inquiries about new matters to that partner. If you have no prior contact with us, please fill out the adjacent form, or email us at inquiries@kp-lf.com, and an appropriate partner will respond to your query.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/889018c645a31e38869fb52889fddb5512d07c8a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-service-inquiries/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">61249887-3342-40a6-8646-0d4f1e1dc396</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Billing & invoicing]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Billing & invoicing</h1><p>Where the billable hour is the appropriate remuneration model, we are quite accustomed to comprehensive budgeting and reporting, which put our clients fully in control of their running and anticipated costs. Where possible, we take an open and flexible approach to billing models, combining one-off and recurring payments with completion-time and success fees, to achieve the best possible match of costs to value.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/889018c645a31e38869fb52889fddb5512d07c8a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-billing-and-invoicing/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9ec473c1-710e-4191-b10d-6d1b0b6f81be</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Working at KP]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Working at KP</h1><p>If you would like to discuss opportunities to work with us, in a demanding and rewarding environment, please fill out our inquiries form attaching a comprehensive resume, or email us directly at inquiries@kp-lf.com, and one of our partners will be in contact with you.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/889018c645a31e38869fb52889fddb5512d07c8a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-working-at-kp/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e35b8fa0-6479-4204-aeaa-660b1352ad2c</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Sovereign Finance]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Sovereign Finance</h1><p>We are at the forefront of the law and practice related to the sovereign debt crisis. Partners at KP have established track records advising managers of general syndicated and special sovereign issues, as well as large portfolio managers on secondary market transactions.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2504b14633302780edf592d064ee537b5f958ff9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kpgrid/kp-or-sovereign-finance/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f55ab086-83d7-4703-ad5d-75ea65cde82b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:33:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KP | Expertise]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KP | Expertise</h1><p>KP is a broad niche practice serving international and domestic commercial and industrial corporates, financial institutions, and natural persons facing critical and high impact situations, in contentious and non-contentious matters within its fields of expertise.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/889018c645a31e38869fb52889fddb5512d07c8a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.kp-lf.com/Expertise/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">61c3f3fc-b7e1-4276-8307-f1c5e135e083</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:28:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>